Guide to the Peter Burton papers circa 1960-2008.
Burton, Peter
- Series IV. Personal Reference Collection
  - Alphabetical by Name
    - King William III (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Kenneth Williams (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Tennessee Williams (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Angus Wilson (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Mari Wilson (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Dutchess of Windsor (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - Stevie Wonder (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Ron Wood (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - DJ Mrs. Woood (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Graeme Woolaston (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Virginia Woolf (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - People "Y" (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Yello (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Paul Young (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Young Rascals (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - People "Z" (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Jean-Paul Zaccarini (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Filing (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Photographs/Illustrations To Be Filed 1 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Photographs/Illustrations To Be Filed 2 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Alphabetical by Subject
    - Autobiographical Material (Box 12, Folder 151)
    - Art (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - Arts - Comments Relating to Clause 28 (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - Books (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - Classical Music(ians) (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Dance (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Dance: Adventures in Motion Pictures (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Dance: American Ballet Theatre (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Dance: The Australian Ballet (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Dance: Ballet Rambert (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Dance: The Bolshoi Ballet (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Dance: Michael Clark (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Dance: Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Dance: Dutch National Ballet (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Dance: DV8 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Dance: English National Ballet (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Dance: Jan Fabre (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Dance: Bill T. Jones (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Dance: Lindsay Kemp (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Dance: Kirov (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Dance: London Contemporary Dance Theatre (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Dance: London Festival Ballet (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Dance: Stephen Petronio (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Dance: Rambert Dance Company (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Dance: Royal Ballet (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Dance: Royal Winnipeg Ballet (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Dance: Sadler's Wells Royal Ballet (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Gay--Useful Cuttings (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Obituaries (Gay) (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Opera (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Plays (Gay) 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Plays (Gay) 2 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Press Cuttings (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Restaurants (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Revue (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Television (Gay) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Theatre 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Theatre 2 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Theatre (Gay) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Press Cuttings (Legal Sized)
    - Press Cuttings, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Press Cuttings, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Press Cuttings, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Press Cuttings, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Press Cuttings, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Press Cuttings, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Press Cuttings, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Press Cuttings, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Press Cuttings, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Press Cuttings, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Additional Oversized Materials
    - Cats (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Johnny Cougar (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Pam's Birthday Book (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Rod Stewart and the Faces Programs (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - William Lawrence Interview in Evening Argus Weekend (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Maugham Diaries in The Sunday Review (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - The Ghost Ship (by Robin Maugham) in Today (Box 15, Folder 7)